Guide to the Records of the North American Jewish Students Appeal, undated, 1962, 1964-1996 (bulk 1971-1995) *I-338 and *I-338A
Center for Jewish History, Publisher.
- Series II: Organizational Records, undated, 1971-1996; Boxes 16 (Folders 4-17) - Box 33.
  - Subseries 1: General Records, 1970-1996; Boxes 16 (Folders 4-17) - Box 27.
    - American Zionist Youth Foundation University Student Department (USD/AZYF) Correspondence, Memos and Updates, 1990-1993 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - American Zionist Youth Foundation University Student Department (USD/AZYF) Flyers, Brochures, Press Releases and Articles, 1990-1993 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - American Zionist Youth Foundation University Student Department (USD/AZYF) Guides and Addresses, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Annual Register of Grant Support Correspondence, 1984-1985, 1990, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Anti-Defamation League of B'Nai B'Rith Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Anti-Semitism/Anti-Zionism on Campus Clippings, undated, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Association of Jewish Community Organization Personnel (AJCOP) Correspondence and Memos, 1987-1990 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Board of Jewish Education Correspondence, 1976-1978, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Brandeis University Professional Advisory Committee of the Horstein Program in Jewish Communal Service Correspondence, 1987, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Brochure Mock-Ups, [1971-1974] (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Brochure Mock-Ups and Correspondence, undated, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - By-Laws, undated, [1975] (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Campus Campaign Drives Correspondence and List of Chairmen, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Campus Campaign Drives Correspondence, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Campus Campaign Drives Correspondence and Fundraising Guide, 1975-1976 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Campus Campaign Drives Donation Correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Campus National Committee of Small Cities Questionnaire Responses, March 1976 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Canada Dept. of Finance and General Consulate Correspondence, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Canadian Unions of Jewish Students (Menachem Kellner) Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Center for Learning and Leadership (CLAL) Correspondence, Proposals, Reports and Notes, undated, 1988-1993 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Certificate of Incorporation and Correspondence, undated, 1971-1972 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Central Conference of American Rabbis Correspondence, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Clippings, undated, 1971-1972, 1976-1977, 1985-1986, 1989, 1992-1994 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Commission for the Absorption of Soviet Émigrés Correspondence, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Commission of American Jewish Life Correspondence, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Conference on Alternatives in Jewish Education (CAJE) Program Brochure, Flyers, and Poster (Northern Illinois University, DeKalb, IL, August 11-15), 1985 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Conference of Jewish Communal Service (CJCS) Correspondence, Memos and Programs (See Box 23, Folder 9-11: Jewish Communal Service Association (JCSA)), 1988-1994
    - Conference on Jewish Women (Second Annual) Proposal, [1974] (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Constitution, undated, 1979-1984 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Constitution, 1985-1989 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, A-H, undated, 1971-1993 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, I-O, 1971-1994 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, P-Z, 1971-1993 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence - Faxes Received, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence - Faxes Sent, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Council on Jewish Manpower Associations, 1976-1977 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Dialogue/Dor Hemshech Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Direct Mail Campaign, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Direct Mail Campaign, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Direct Mail Campaign, 1986-1987 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Direct Mail Campaign, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Direct Mail Campaign-Oram Group Proposal and Correspondence, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Direct Mail Resources and Drafts, [1984] (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Draft Proposal Regarding the APPEAL, undated, [1971], [1975] (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Encyclopedia of Associations Entries, 1978, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - E.R.S. Printing Drafts and Receipts, 1977-1985 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Federal Proposed Projects (NEH) Request for Information, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies of New York Correspondence and Course Listings, 1972, 1974-1976 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Field Work Activities File - Howard Creed, 1987 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Flame, The (Or Chadash/New Light) Correspondence, Notes and Flyers, [1982] (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Flyers and Handouts, undated, 1970s-1990s (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Forms and Letter Samples, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Friends of Jewish Students Newsletter, Fall 1971, June 1972 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Friends of Jewish Students Newsletter Drafts and Correspondence, undated, 1971, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Gevertz, Brenda "Choosing a College Jewishly" Article, Correspondence and Resume, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Greater New York Conference on Soviet Jewry Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Greenberg, Irving (Rabbi) Benefit for NAJSA Correspondence, Lists and Invitations, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Haber (William) Award Nomination, undated, [1988] (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Hebrew Union College-Jewish Institute of Religion Advisory Board Correspondence, Article and Reports, undated, 1971, 1974, 1983, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Hillel Annual Conference of Hillel Professionals Conference Packet and Program, 1989, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Hillel Annual Conference of Hillel Professionals Conference Packet, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Hillel Annual Conference of Hillel Professionals Conference Packet, [1994?] (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Hillel Correspondence and Memos, 1974-1979 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Hillel Correspondence and Memos, 1980-1989 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Hillel Correspondence and Memos, undated, 1990-1995 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Hillel Leaders Assembly Memos, Program and Resource, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Hillel Leaders Assembly Memos, Course Descriptions and Schedule, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Hillel National Jewish Student Issues Conference Programs and Flyers, 1987-1989 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Hillel Partner Agency Meeting Agenda and Notes, May 23, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Hillel Rabbis Contributions Correspondence and Campaign Planning Document, 1972-1973 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Hillel-University of Michigan 16th Annual Conference on the Holocaust Program and Clipping, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Histadrut - General Federation of Labour in Israel, International Department, Diaspora Section, 1971, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Iken, Ronald S., "American Jewish Community is Democratic, and If Not, It Shouldn't Be" Graduate Paper, January 27, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - In Process Materials File, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Institute for Non-Profit Management Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Inter-Generational Jewish Activists Meeting, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Intermarriage Symposium Correspondence and Reports, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Intermarriage Symposium Proceedings and Publication, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Internships Applications and Evaluations, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Internships Applications and Evaluations, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Internships Applications and Evaluations, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Israeli and American Jewish Contact Lists, [1974] (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Israel Campus Activities Committee (CAC) Memos, Correspondence, Meeting Summaries and Articles, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Israel Campus Activities Committee (CAC) Memos, Correspondence, Meeting Summaries and Articles, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Israel Campus Activities Committee (CAC) Memos, Correspondence, Meeting Summaries and Articles, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Israeli Consulate (N.Y.) Correspondence, Press Releases, Election Guide, Memos, 1974, 1976-1977, 1991-1993 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Israeli Consulate (N.Y.) Office of Academic Affairs Project Materials and Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Israeli/Palestinian Conflict Background Articles, 1980s (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Jewish Association for College Youth (JACY) Correspondence and Memos, 1971-1977 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Jewish Association for College Youth (JACY) Memos, Correspondence, Subsidy Applications and Pamphlets, 1978-1986 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Jewish Association for College Youth (JACY) Memos, 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Jewish Association for College Youth (JACY) Mayer Fellowship Intern Agenda, Memos and Report, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - (Conference of) Jewish Communal Service Association (JCSA) Annual Meeting and Correspondence, undated, 1976, 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - (Conference of) Jewish Communal Service Association (JCSA) Annual Meeting and Correspondence, undated, 1990-1992 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - (Conference of) Jewish Communal Service Association (JCSA) Social Work Students Proposal, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Jewish Community Relations Council (JCRC) of New York Media Guidelines and Correspondence, undated, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Jewish Funders Network Conference Materials, 1993-1995 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Jewish Telegraphic Agency Correspondence and Bulletins, 1971-1972, 1978, 1983-1984, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Jewish Theological Seminary of America Correspondence, 1979, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Jewish Week/Breira Controversy Correspondence, Clippings and Publication, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Jewish Welfare Board (JWB) Office Space Correspondence, 1975-1987 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Jewish Welfare Board (JWB) Sample Allocation Packet, [1975] (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - (American Jewish) Joint Distribution Committee (JDC), 1990-1992 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Lecturers and Program Leaders Correspondence and Information, undated, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Lilith Correspondence and Clippings, 1976, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - MCI Telephone Billing Correspondence, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Mission Statement, undated (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - National Conference on Jewish Women and Men (Network) Agenda, Report, Grant Applications, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - National Conference on Soviet Jewry Program and Materials, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - National Jewish Community Relations Advisory Council (NJCRAC) Meetings Background Information Memoranda, 1991-1992 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - National Jewish Community Relations Advisory Council (NJCRAC) Meetings Background Information Memoranda, 1993-1994 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - National Jewish Conference Center Planning Correspondence, Minutes, Proposals and Notes, 1974-1975 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - National Organizations Miscellaneous Brochures, Pamphlets and Newsletters, [1991-1993] (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - National Yiddish Book Exchange Prospectus, Catalog and Newsletter, [1985] (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - New York Board of Rabbis (First Annual) Israel Opportunities and Aliyah Conference Cooperating Agency Planning and Program Materials, 1985-1986 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - New York NETWORK (American Jewish Committee Women's Forum) Announcements and Minutes, 1983-1986 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - New York Telephone and Constituent Payment Correspondence and Bills, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - North American Chavuroth and Assorted Simchas (N.A.C.H.A.S) Conference Planning Correspondence, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Office Equipment, Computer, Postal and Telephone Agreements and Correspondence, undated, 1981-1994 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Office Equipment, Misc. Agreements and Correspondence, undated, 1980s-1990s (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Office Inventory (APPEAL, NETWORK, JSPS), 1976 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Office Space Correspondence, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Operations Procedures and Structure Description, undated, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Options Publishing Co. Newsletter Correction, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Pan-American Jewish Students' Conference (WUJS) Correspondence and Report, 1973-1975 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Partispayan, Willen and Zina (Soviet Jewry Family) Correspondence, 1977-1980 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Postmaster General Certification and Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Press Releases, undated, 1976, 1979-1986, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Project Dorot Elderly Program Correspondence and Grant Application, 1976-1977, 1984 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Promotional and Publicity Materials, undated, [1970s-1990s] (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Prospective New York Donors Correspondence, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Public Interest/Public Relations (PIPR) Workshop, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Radius Institute for Not-for-Profit Management (Columbia University) Seminar Announcements and Memos, 1980-1983 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Raleigh Lithograph Company Correspondence, Bills and Mock-ups, undated, 1976, 1980-1981 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Reinberg, Evgeny and Sophia (Soviet Jewry Family) Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Rules of Order, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Small Cities Executive Institute Conference and Presentation Materials (Tamarack Lodge, Greenfield Park, NY, August 17-24), 1975 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Speaking Engagements Correspondence, 1973 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Spitzer Forum on Public Policy (B'Nai B'Rith/Hillel Foundations) Correspondence, Notes, and Program Guide (Washington, DC, October 28-30), 1990 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Spitzer Forum on Public Policy (B'Nai B'Rith/Hillel Foundations) Correspondence and Program (Washington, DC, October 20-22), 1991 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Spitzer Forum on Public Policy (B'Nai B'Rith/Hillel Foundations) Correspondence, Workshop Information and Program (Los Angeles, CA, January 24-26), 1993 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Spitzer Forum on Public Policy (B'Nai B'Rith/Hillel Foundations) Correspondence, Workshop Information and Program (Philadelphia, PA, February 6-8), 1994 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Stationary Samples, NAJSA, Constituents and Organizations, undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Stock Donations, 1971 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Supportive Community Facts for Funding: NCJCS Inter-Disciplinary Session on Jewish Education Report, [1972] (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Union of American Hebrew Congregations (UAHC) College Education Department Correspondence and Flyers, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - United Synagogue of Conservative Judaism Department of College Outreach/KOACH Correspondence and Outreach Guides, 1992-1994 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Varet, Elizabeth "Visions and Voices" Conference Correspondence, 1992-1995 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - V.I.P. In the Jewish World Encyclopedia Entry, 1981-1982 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - "Visions and Voices" Interfaith Marriage Symposium Arrangements and Correspondence, undated, 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - "Visions and Voices" Interfaith Marriage Symposium Registrations and Evaluation, undated, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - "Visions and Voices" Interfaith Marriage Symposium Visual Aids and Questionnaire, undated, [1993] (Box 111, Folder 7 (OS))
    - Washington 1: National Jewish Student Conference On Public Policy Issues Program (Washington, DC, October 13-17), 1982 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - West Side Cluster Salary Reimbursement Memos, 1979-1980 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Williams and Co. Rental Disputes Correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Wisconsin, State of; Dept. of Regulation and Licensing Charitable Organizations Correspondence and Memos, 1980 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - "Women and Leadership: A Conference of the Task Force on the Jewish Woman Commission on Synagogue Relations" Workshop Materials, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - World Jewish Congress (WJC) Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - World Jewish Congress (WJC) Conference on Soviet Jewry (Brussels, Belgium) Correspondence, Memos and Newsletter, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - World Jewish Congress (WJC) Youth Commission Correspondence, Minutes, Memos, and Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - World Union of Jewish Students (WUJS) Correspondence, 1971-1974 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - World Union of Jewish Students (WUJS) Correspondence, 1975-1978 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - World Union of Jewish Students (WUJS) Correspondence, 1979-1984, 1990-1991 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - World Union of Jewish Students (WUJS) Institute (Arad, Israel)-Clive Lessen Correspondence and Program, 1992 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - World Union of Jewish Students (WUJS) Summer Seminar in Israel Information, Correspondence, Brochure and Application, 1992-1993 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - World Zionist Organization (WZO) Correspondence, 1974, 1992, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Yom Kippur War Information Packet, October 1973 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Subseries 2: Financial Records, 1971-1995; Boxes 29-34. (Box 33 contains restricted materials. Box 34 is OS 2.)
    Arrangement is in alphabetical order.
    The NAJSA acted primarily as an umbrella fundraising arm for its Constituents. Therefore, a large portion of the collection in several series is devoted to financial matters. The most concentrated of these records can be found in Subseries 2: Financial Records, which document the overall financial transactions of the NAJSA including allocations received from Federations, income, deposit and expenditures records, financial statements of the APPEAL (Constituent statements may be found in Series III), accountants correspondence, tax returns (the 1975 return was not found in the collection), Trustee and Friend contributions and employee records (restricted material). In accordance with records management procedures, certain unnecessary information regarding financial records have been discarded. Among these records are: cancelled checks and check stub registers, deposit slips, payroll registers, petty cash receipts, banking statements and bills for messengers; office supplies, computer equipment, and telephone bills. (Telephone bills regarding disputes between NAJSA and their Constituents have been retained.) Cancelled checks regarding tax payments (federal, quarterly and payroll) have been retained. Related financial records may be found in Series III: Constituents and Series V: Federations (Subseries 1: Council for Jewish Federations,Subseries 3: Large City Budgeting Conference and Subseries 5: U.S. Cities and Canada). Documentation relating to fundraising conducted by the NAJSA to garner grants from national foundations may be found in Series VI: Fundraising.
    - Allocations Received Record - Federations, 1971-1979 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Allocations Received Record - Federations, 1979-1992 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Allocations Received Record - Federations, 1989-1995 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Allocations Received History-Intermediate Cities (Jewish Population of 5,000-40,000), 1973-1976 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Allocations Request History, 1971-1973 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Allocations to Constituents and Beneficiary Grants, undated, 1974-1976, 1982-1984, 1988 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Bank Correspondence, 1970s-1990s (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Budgets and Proposed Budgets, 1971-1982 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Cash Income Records, 1978-1986 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Deposit Records, 1991-1994 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Direct Mail Campaign Contributions Record, 1985-1989 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Expenditures Record, 1991-1994 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - "Fair Share" Constituent Guidelines, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Financial Statements, 1972-1976 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Financial Statements, 1977-1980 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Financial Statements, 1981-1985 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Financial Statements, 1986-1988 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Financial Statements, 1988-1994 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Foundation and Grant Awards Record, 1990-1992 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Friends and Rabbis Contributions Record, 1971-1994 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Heartland Marketing Donation Campaign Record, 1991-1992 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Internal Revenue Correspondence, 1972-1994 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Insurance Policies, 1989-1995 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Insurance Policy Correspondence, 1987-1994 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Kramer Fund Campaign, 1990-1991 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Kramer Fund Campaign, 1994-1995 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Loan Contracts and Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - New York State Department of Charitable Organization Annual Reports and Correspondence, 1972-1991 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - New York State Department of Law Correspondence, 1977-1989 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - New York State Department of Taxation and Finance Correspondence, 1973-1991 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Quarterly Comparative Figures, 1975-1985 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Schwinger, Simons and Co., Accountants Correspondence, undated, 1971-1978 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Sobel and Co. Accountants Correspondence, 1978-1984 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Sobel and Co. Accountants Correspondence, 1985-1989 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Sobel and Co. Accountants Correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - State Insurance Fund Payments and Correspondence, 1971-1987 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - State Insurance Fund Payments and Correspondence, 1988-1995 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Tax Returns, 1971-1974, 1976-1987 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Tax Returns, 1988-1993 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Trustees Contributions Record, 1971-1993 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Workmen's Circle Correspondence and Policies, 1975-1980 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Employee Documentation RESTRICTED, 1985, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Employee Unemployment Insurance Claims RESTRICTED, 1976-1979 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Fox, Robin Work File RESTRICTED, 1992-1993 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Gevertz, Brenda Work File RESTRICTED, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Gibson, Darlene Work File RESTRICTED, 1976-1979 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Keenan, Catherine Work File RESTRICTED, 1990-1991 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Mishan, Marc Work File RESTRICTED, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Ovadia, Seth Work File RESTRICTED, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Valentino, Evelyn Work File RESTRICTED, 1979-1987 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Wage and Withholding Tax Returns RESTRICTED, 1977-1994 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - University of Illinois D'Varim Publishing Grant (From Series IV, Box 59 Folder 38) RESTRICTED, 1992-1993 (Box 33 (59), Folder 11 (38))
    - Constituent Allocation Ledger, undated, 1979-1987, 1989-1990 (Box 34 OS 2, Folder 1)
    - Expenditures Ledger, 1971-1982, 1987-1992 (Box 34 OS 2, Folder 2)
    - Federation Allocation Ledger, undated, 1977-1990 (Box 34 OS 2, Folder 3)
    - Income Ledger, 1971-1982, 1987-1992 (Box 34 OS 2, Folder 4)
    - Tax Payments - Cancelled Checks, 1972-1993 (Box 34 OS 2, Folder 5)
    - Trustee and Friends Contributions Ledger, 1978-1990 (Box 34 OS 2, Folder 6)
- Series III: Constituent Files, undated, 1962, 1964-1995 (bulk 1971-1995); Boxes 35-51.
  Arranged in eight series, one general records series, and seven subsequent series by Constituent in alphabetical order. Records for Constituents Lights in Action and the Bayit Project may be found in the General Records series.